# Rampi Federico Daniel Full Stack Developer

federampi@gmail.com

Paso de los Libres, Corrientes - Argentina.

Portfolio LinkedIn GitHub

### **ABOUT ME**

I am a **Full Stack Web Developer** and computer technician, I have experience working with JavaScript, React, Redux, Express.js, among others. I consider myself a proactive person, with logical thinking, I do well working in a team because I believe that cooperation is the best method to solve problems and to meet the objectives.

I am a curious person, who is always reading about new technologies and different methods or ways to improve my code.

My goals are, to put into practice the skills I have developed, to continue learning new technologies and best practices, also to join a team and collaborate with my experience. I am open to all opportunities that allow me to grow either as **Front end**, **Back end** or **Full stack**.

# **SKILLS:**

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Tailwind CSS
- React
- Redux
- Node.js
- Express.js
- Git y Github
- Postman
- Sequelize
- PostgreSQL

### **PROJECTS**

### Full Stack Web Developer - Pi Pokemon

Henry Bootcamp, Buenos Aires, Argentina.

- Design and develop a pokemon App that includes: pokemon search, pokemon detail display, filtering, sorting, paging and creation.
- For the development I used React, Redux, pure CSS for the **Front end** and Node.js, Express for the **Back end**. Database in PostgreSQL and Sequelize.

Repository | Deploy

### **Weather App**

• It is a SPA, where an API (OpenWeathermap) is consumed. You can search for the city you want to see, it will be displayed on the screen with the temperature, the country and an image of the weather, you can delete that we no longer want to see. Also in More Details option you can see more information about the city.

Repository | Deploy

### **Clone Mercado Libre**

• Project based on the MercadoLibre Challenge, but this time we made a clone of the MercadoLibre home page and consumed its API to give it some functionalities such as, search items with results view and also filtering, item details showing also questions asked by users.

Repository | Deploy

### **Git Hub App**

• I have developed a web application using React and Tailwind CSS on the frontend, and Express.js for path creation. The application consumes the GitHub API, using the link-header package to implement the pagination provided by the API itself.

Repository | Deploy

### Full Stack Web Developer - Henry Bank

Henry Bootcamp, Buenos Aires, Argentina.

- Design and develop an App-mobile that includes: searches, filtering, sorting, user registration, login with authentication, administrator panel, user profile, news, payment gateway and transfers, fixed term, buying and selling cryptocurrencies, mailing system, etc.
- For the development we used React Navite, CSS, Redux, Figma for the **Front end** and Node.js with Express for the **Back end**. Database in PostgresSQL and Sequelize. JWT was used for authentication, Nodemailer for mailing and Stripe for card payments.
- In this project I worked on the **Back end** side, we worked using the SCRUM methodology where we used Trello to write down the tasks to be done.

Frontend repository | Backend repository | Demo

# Rampi Federico Daniel Full Stack Developer

### **LANGUAGES**

• Spanish: C2 (Native)

• Portuguese: C2 (Basic)

• Ingles: B1 Intermediate EF SET Certificate)

### PROFESSIONAL EDUCATION

### **Full stack Developer**

Bootcamp Soy Henry | Feb. 2022 - Ag. 2022 |

700 hours of theoretical and practical courses.

#### IT infrastructure technician

Instituto Superior De Formación Docente Profesor Agustín Gómez | Feb 2012 - Dic 2013

• Career focused on preventive and corrective maintenance of computers, both hardware and software, also focused on the installation and maintenance of computer networks.

### **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

### Freelancer Full Stack Web Developer

Oct. 2022 - Present

My main focus has been on developing attractive and functional user interfaces using Front end technologies such as JavaScript, React.js, Redux and Tailwind CSS. I have worked on several projects that demonstrate my ability to manipulate and access data effectively on the Front end. In addition, I have used backend technologies such as Express.js and MongoDB, as well as the Mongoose

In addition, I have used backend technologies such as Express.js and MongoDB, as well as the Mongoose ORM, to create web services that integrate with the Front end. I have also worked with relational databases using PostgreSQL and Sequelize ORM. In some of my projects, I have implemented authentication and password encryption using JWT.

With my ability to work with Front end and Back end technologies, I am ready to face any challenge in web development and create impressive projects that exceed client's expectations.

### Technical Support Jan 2014 – Jul 2022

Paso de los Libres, Corrientes, Argentina

Repair and maintenance of desktop and notebook computers, etc. Both hardware and software, installation of programs, operating systems, office packs, etc.

Back-up of files and file recovery, installation of network cable (UTP), installation of cameras, etc.

# IT Technical Support | Intern at Paso de los Libres Customs Office

Ag. 2013 - Nov. 2013

Paso de los Libres, Corrientes, Argentina

Maintenance and installation of wired and wireless networks, repair of computer equipment, both software and hardware, repair of printers, etc.